{
    "subject": "resource/Tour_de_France_(song)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Songs_written_by_Ralf_H\u00fctter",
    "human_readable": "The song 'Tour de France' is about songs written by Ralf H\u00fctter.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9563401341438293,
            "question": "Who wrote the songs that 'Tour de France' is about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.899418294429779,
            "question": "What is the song 'Tour de France' about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7204864621162415,
            "question": "Are there any other songs by Ralf H\u00fctter that are about songs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6891363263130188,
            "question": "Who is Ralf H\u00fctter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6853475570678711,
            "question": "What is unique about the lyrics in 'Tour de France'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6325691938400269,
            "question": "What genre of music might 'Tour de France' be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4802897274494171,
            "question": "Is the song 'Tour de France' a tribute to cycling?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3211402893066406,
            "question": "Do you think the title 'Tour de France' is ironic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31957104802131653,
            "question": "How might 'Tour de France' make a listener feel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06643399596214294,
            "question": "Can you imagine other song titles inspired by this concept?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The song 'Tour de France' is about songs written by Ralf H\u00fctter.",
            "html": "dbpedia_32_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might 'Tour de France' make a listener feel?",
            "html": "dbpedia_32_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you think the title 'Tour de France' is ironic?",
            "html": "dbpedia_32_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is the song 'Tour de France' a tribute to cycling?",
            "html": "dbpedia_32_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_32_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_32_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_32_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_32_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_32_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_32_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_32_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_32_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_32_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_32_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information that the song \"Tour de France\" is indeed a creation of Ralf H\u00fctter, who was one of Kraftwerk's lead artists. This supports the statement that the song is about songs written by Ralf H\u00fctter."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text states that \"Tour de France\" was written by Ralf H\u00fctter and Maxime Schmitt.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}